meetmindful.com 2015-03-19

# Privacy Policy - MeetMindful | Online Dating Evolved

This Privacy Policy describes what information we collect, how we may use it, whom we may share it with, and the options you have. By using our website, you are agreeing to the terms outlined here.

If you have any further questions, please do not hesitate to contact us.

## What we collect

We may collect your name, email address, and other personal information through our website.

We may collect and store any personal information you enter on our website or on a mobile application, or provide to us in some other manner. This includes identifying information, such as your name, address, email address and telephone number, and, if you transact business with us, financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information). You may also provide us information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information such as your hometown or your username.

We use various technologies to collect information from your device and about your activities on our site or application.

We automatically collect information from your browser or device when you visit our website or application. This information could include your IP address, device ID, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us, and the referring website address.

When you visit our website or application, we may assign your device one or more  **cookies** , to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the pages you visit, the time and date of your visits, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site. During your visits to other websites or applications where we advertise, we (or third parties) may use certain data collected on our site to show you MeetMindful.com advertisements. If you choose to  **decline cookies** , please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on our website. No personally identifiable information is contained in these cookies.

We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our site.

We may allow service providers, advertising companies, ad networks and other third parties, to display advertisements on our site. We do not not provide any non-anonymized personal information to these third parties.

## What happens with that information

We may use information that we collect about you to:

  * deliver our products and services, and manage our business;
  * manage your account and provide you with customer support;
  * perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others;
  * communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or other third parties;
  * develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our site and other sites, including providing our advertisements to you when you visit other sites;
  * perform ad tracking and website or mobile application analytics;
  * verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes;
  * enforce or exercise any rights in our terms and conditions;
  * perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

We may use financial information or payment method information to (i) process payment for any purchases made on our website or application, (ii) enroll you in the discount, rebate, and other programs in which you elect to participate, (iii) to protect against or identify possible fraudulent transactions, and (iv) otherwise as needed to manage our business.

## Who we may share your information with:

We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated in this Privacy Policy or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your personal information shared. We may share personal information with:

We may share information, including personal information, with third parties that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, providing customer service (including through our users who moderate flagged content for the MeetMindful community) and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, ad tracking and analytics, member screenings, supporting our website functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our website. We may also share your name, contact information and credit card information with our service providers who process credit card payments.

These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.

When you register or make purchases on our website or click-through our advertisements offered on third party websites or applications, we may share personal information with the businesses with which we partner to offer you the applicable products, services or any advertisements. When you elect to engage in a particular merchant’s offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant.

When you make purchases on our website or click-through our advertisements offered on third party websites, we may share personal information with the businesses with which we partner to offer you the applicable products, services or advertisements. When you elect to engage in a particular merchant’s offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant.

We also may disclose your information, including personal information:

In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.

When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce our website terms and conditions or other agreements or policies.

In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

We may share non-personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated, non-personal, or personal information in hashed, non-human readable form, information with third parties, including advisors, writers, researchers, partners, advertisers and investors for the purpose of conducting general business analysis, studies, articles, and essays media and entertainment or other business purposes. For example, we may engage a data provider who may collect web log data from you (including IP address and information about your browser or operating system), or place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us (such as your email address), that we may share with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form.

## Accessing your information

If you have an online account with us, you have the ability to review and update your personal information online by logging into your account and clicking on Settings. More information about how to contact us is provided below. If you have an online account with us, you also may delete or disable your account at any time by visiting the “Settings” page for your account. If you delete or disable your account, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and record keeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, enforce our terms and conditions, take actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of our website or our users, or take other actions otherwise permitted by law. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties’ policies.

## Your choices about collection and use of your information

You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our website because such information may be required in order for you to register as a member; purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions on our website.

When you register on our website, you consent to receive email messages from us. You may be given the opportunity, in any commercial email that we send to you, to opt out of receiving such messages in the future. We request a reasonable time to process an opt-out request. We may send you other types of transactional and relationship email communications, such as service announcements, administrative notices, and surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. Please note that changing information in your account, or otherwise opting out of receipt of promotional email communications, will only affect future activities or communications from us. If we have already provided your information to a third party (such as a service provider) before you have changed your preferences or updated your information, you may have to change you preferences directly with that third party.

Our applications may also deliver notifications to your phone or mobile device.

## How we protect your personal information

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. We want you to feel confident using our website to transact business. However, no system can be completely secure.

Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or other communications will always remain secure. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information and should avoid sending personal information through insecure email.

## Information you provide about yourself while using our service

We provide areas on our websites where you can post information about yourself and others and communicate with others or upload content such as photographs. In addition, such postings may appear on other websites or when searches are executed on the subject of your posting. Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information.

## No Rights of Third Parties

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the website.
